You
Right, so where are we on the island? Let's steal an accompany card so we can go somewhere
Uninvited guests, huh?
Hmm makes me nervous
Just to be sure you folks aren't castaways. Are you I?
Doubt it since the strong currents around the island make it virtually impossible to drift here by accident
This guy's tough
Who the hell are you?
He's supposed to be our guide or something. No, I'm just one of the creators of this game. You can call me Razor. I
mainly handle the emissive systems like
traveling by spell and trespassers
This spell can only be used by a game master
Sorry, but you'll have to leave
Come back the right way and you'll be welcome here
There's an excellent item in the game that you can obtain by fighting me
So if you decide to play we'll probably get to fight eventually
Fine then we'll be right back through the front door next time
Eliminate on
Huh, that's one intimidating group of people I can tell you that
Hmm
Yeah
They've got aог
All right
Oh
Until first we sail.
Thanks for taking us.
Its photographic colors.
contractors take us on display.
I can't be alone.
You can smile again
You can fly away
The world is shining for you
The sun is shining for you
You can fly away
Your eyes are shining for you
You can't reach your eyes
As Gon continues to train, he discovers a hint to developing his ultimate technique.
Show me rock! Come on!
John Ken Rock!
Whoa!
I see.
Next up!
All right, show me rock!
John Ken Paper!
Whiskey, how do I make my nen fly?
Train more!
Paper is an emitter technique?
Uh-huh.
And scissors is a transmuter.
Pretty soon, I want to try to cut through a rock!
Understood. That's a reasonable fighting technique.
But a childish idea.
I can focus my nen in my fist, but you know how it takes a lot of time?
I was trying to figure out a good way that I could spend that time.
When you were talking about the game, it just hit me.
Because I like that game.
Hmm.
It's important to trust in your instincts.
Those gut feelings play a big role in techniques that require multiple categories.
The real key is that it should feel right to you.
Well, this is all I've got right now.
But if I charge it up, it's pretty strong.
That's awesome, Killua!
You're like an electric eel!
Awful analogy.
Come on, man.
What?
He can change aura into electricity at his age?
It's frightening.
Not to mention, tragic.
His childhood must have been a living hell.
In fact, it's a miracle that he can smile at all anymore.
Oh, look at them.
They make such a great team.
Well, what do you say?
Should we call it a day?
Huh?
It's a bit early, but how about a party?
Party?
What do you boys do to celebrate back home?
Celebrate?
It's almost New Year's in the real world, isn't it?
Time flows at the same speed in here as it does outside.
Oh, no!
Hmm?
I forgot!
The deadline for the hunter exhibit coming up!
Oh, man.
And right when training was starting to get kind of fun, too.
If my memory serves, you have to apply by year's end.
Then we need to hurry!
But remind me how we get outside again?
I'm guessing there are spell cards to leave the game, right?
There are.
So let's take another trip to Masadora.
All right!
Now, let's find a place to have some tea.
We can't.
We don't have much time.
We can ask at the stores we go to.
You want to leave the island?
No sweat.
That'll be 3,000 jenny.
If you go about 50 kilometers west, you'll reach the island's only port.
You'll have to defeat or bribe the harbormaster.
If you do, you'll get a ticket that'll transport you outside.
How big of a bribe do you think?
That depends on how he's feeling.
Yeah, okay.
Your other option is to use a leave spell card.
But that one is pretty rare, so...
What do we do?
Head to the port.
Since it's a rare card, it might not even show up no matter how much we spend.
Yeah, you're right.
Voila!
Well, I guess now I'll go ace the exam and come right back.
First, go to the lone cedar tree that's down by Dole Harbor.
Magical beasts called Kiriko live there.
Just tell them that you're my friend, and they'll take you right to the exam site.
Will do.
See ya!
All right then.
Let's get back to your training.
Us!
Welcome, sir.
Is this where I started?
No, it's not.
The girl looks familiar, though.
But that's pretty typical for games.
Will you be leaving the island now?
If so, please specify your location.
Do you have Dole Harbor?
Yes, I do.
Then just send me there.
I understand.
When you leave this island, all of the cards that are in your free slots will be deleted instantly.
Do you accept that?
Yeah, that's fine.
Well, in that case, we will be patiently awaiting your return, sir.
Guess I'm back in the real world now, huh?
Doesn't feel any different.
And book.
So it doesn't work out here.
Gotcha.
I'll submit my application and head for that cedar tree.
But first, I've got to shower and change.
Okay.
We'll train the whole time you're running.
When you can form numbers zero through nine, all within one minute, you pass.
Huh?
That hurt!
What in the world are you doing?
Huh?
Aren't you...
I can see that your other friend isn't with you.
What's that thing on your shoulder?
What happened to you?
Is something wrong?
The bomber got us.
Hear me out.
I have something to say.
So he was the bomber.
The others are back in our hideout, waiting for him to disarm the bombs.
They believe in the terms he gave them, but I'm not as convinced.
Now what?
What can we do?
If they're prepared to accept casualties...
Won't happen.
The very first ones to jump him will be the first ones to be sacrificed.
Who would ever volunteer for that?
Good point.
Jispa was the most proficient of us in combat, yet he was beaten instantly.
We were already doomed at that point.
And allowing Genthro to leave the game proved to be a fatal mistake.
We foolishly began to celebrate before we had the chance to verify each member's cards and assigned roles.
And that was when he caught us off guard.
I hate to say it, but I...
I was so distracted that I simply didn't see him use leave until it was too late.
You were probably focused on his explanation, trying to figure out its meaning.
Yeah.
We were thrust into that situation with absolutely no warning at all.
Of course, we were all too stunned to take any action.
I see.
But may I ask why you're telling us all this?
Out of everyone I've met here on the island, I believe you're the ones I can rely on the most.
If you communicate with any other players, I beg you to tell them all about the bomber.
If they know about his ability, they can guard against it.
And if it comes down to it, I want you to try to avenge us.
At the very least, do not let him clear the game.
We understand.
Thank you.
I'll use what little time I have left to tell as many as I can about the bomber.
Book.
Return on!
Bunzin!
Actually, the truth of the matter is that when I used Magnetic Force, those two were the only players I could find.
But flattery works wonders.
When it comes to deactivating someone's nin, every thousandth of a percent counts.
Now then, Nyx has probably gone off to meet with the bombers.
However, if what they promised turns out to be a mass-dead nation...
...better get started.
You're finally here.
Now, hand over your ring.
Jispa has passed away.
That's nice.
Your ring?
Disarm everyone's bums first!
Hell no.
First, I have to take that ring back inside the game.
And once I do, I'll confirm that all the cards are indeed in the binder.
Then I'll disarm the bombs.
This is the last time.
Hand over the ring.
Sub, go ahead and put it on.
If you put on a second ring when you're outside the game, your original data gets overwritten.
Mm-hmm.
Now then, let's head back inside together.
Hold on.
What's your name again?
Migamora, Samingadora, Interaminga, Zinberalubra.
Spirits of the forest, remove the unclean nin that is now possessing my body.
Now, what will it be, I wonder?
I call upon the power of the forest spirits and combine it with my own
to create a nin beast capable of consuming the nin abilities of others.
It's a big one.
As I feared, the bomber's countdown is a powerful nin.
So, how'd it go?
Did he disarm them yet?
Now book.
Okay.
81 specified slot card types.
They're here, all right.
Look, we did everything you wanted.
So now, disarm all the bombs.
But of course, I'm a man of my word.
But first, you need to hand over three leave cards.
Okay, then.
Looks like we have a deal.
Sub, borrow.
Here goes.
Release.
I just released all of you from your fear.
That...wasn't...our...deal.
You're all losers, and I don't keep promises to losers. Release doesn't disarm. It's the trigger word.
Leave on!
At least now I don't have to worry about exploding.
But I'm stuck with this guy until Ginthru reverses his ability or dies.
I've got myself a troublesome companion.
Hey, be still!
The bomber's going to kill us all.
He'll assume he succeeded. I'll use it to my advantage.
Bisky?
Hmm?
I think we should go drop by their hideout real fast.
Time's probably already up for them.
Besides, he didn't even tell us where it is.
And even if we could find it, we'd still need a spell card that could take us there and we simply don't have one.
I know. But some of them could have survived the explosion. It's possible.
But doubtful. If the bomber's powerful enough to place bombs on his targets without them noticing, he'd never be that careless.
However, if we just continue to play the game, then we're bound to run into the bomber at some point.
And given that fact, then sooner or later we may need to visit their hideout.
But we still need spell cards. Let's go to Masadora and sell our monster cards to buy some.
Yeah!
Hey, Bisky. How long do you think it'll take me to master my signature move?
Well, you are just starting to develop your Nen. Hard to say when your power and speed will peak.
It is?
That said, I'd be more than a little bit surprised if it took you very long to get the form down.
Really? How long?
Let me see. Hmm.
You may have it ready by the time Keela was back.
All right! I can't wait to see the look on his face when he sees it!
You two are so lucky! We just recently received a huge shipment of different spell cards!
So these are the ones they've been hoarding.
We bought sixty between us, so there are all kinds of types here.
Gon, look!
An S rank? There are only ten in the whole game!
What do you think? Save it? Or should we use it right now?
Hey, don't ask me! I don't know what to do!
Be quiet! Do you want people getting suspicious?
Hmm. If only Keela was still here!
Achoo!
Well, you certainly do smell like Gon!
I miss that kid!
We'll take you to the exam site. Just leave it to us!
Let's hurry. I need to ace it. And then hurry back to Gon right away.
Sure! But the exam won't officially start for a few days!
Oh yeah, that's right.
In the meantime, why don't you tell us all about your adventures with Gon?
Okay. Well, there was that one time that he came to my house.
You're making steady progress, Gon. You're right on track to have your ultimate technique ready.
It helps that this is such a safe place to practice.
With this view, we can spot anyone before they get close enough to use an attack spell.
People are watching for Masadora. I feel it like I felt people watching us at the start point.
But this time, we've got plenty of attack spells.
Hmm. Yes, but just to be safe, I already cast a Blackout Curtain card.
Still, there's no real point in worrying about spell cards.
You just focus on training your hardest.
Us!
Right. It's been a minute.
Next.
Oh, man. It didn't reach far enough.
Don't worry. You're definitely in far better shape than a transmitter would be.
Be patient. Focus on maintaining the shape of your aura.
If you can do it for an extended period of time, you're all set.
Us!
The longer you can maintain that sphere, the stronger your ten is.
And once you've trained long enough, and put in some real effort,
you'll be able to maintain an aura sphere for two or three days at a time.
You should get to where you can reach that rock by the end of the day.
You're right! I got it!
That was quick.
This proves that he's been working hard on his ten and ren every day.
All right. Let's go back to practicing the basics.
Us!
Gon continues to train with Bisky to master his signature technique.
Killua has temporarily left the game to retake the hunter exam.
The boys, each in their own way, are working hard to reach their goals.
Do you have anyoretta pain with us?
Do you want to learn more From the sooner?
Do you want to learn more From the nowtaymeye 가?
Do you want to learn more?
Do you want to learn more from the next time?
I can see…
We'll be right back.
Coming up, the Great Island Tutorial.